Wanted Dead or Dead
Slow West is a western, drama, thriller film directed by John Maclean.
In the Old West, a 17-year-old Scottish boy teams up with a mysterious
gunman to find the woman with whom he is infatuated.
Silas, played by Michael Fassbender.
Jay Cavendish, played by Kodi Smit-McPhee.
Payne, played by Ben Mendelsohn.
Rose Ross, played by Caren Pistorius.
John Ross, played by Rory McCann.
Skelly, played by Eddie Campbell.
Slow West is a 2015 revisionist Western film written and
directed by John Maclean in his directorial debut.
It stars Kodi Smit-McPhee as a young Scotsman searching for his lost love in the
American West, accompanied by a bounty hunter played by Michael Fassbender.
It premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival on 24 January 2015, where it was
awarded the Sundance Institute's World Cinema Jury Prize: Dramatic Winner.
The film was first released on 15 May 2015 in the United States,
with a simultaneous release on video on demand.
The film explores themes of fire, bounty hunter,
horseback riding, shotgun, horse.
The tone is emotional and intense.